A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, LSR family Financial records FA1363
Rockefeller Archive Center
Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, LSR family Financial records
1930-1979
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman (1910-2004)
Rockefeller, Mary French (1910-1997)
FA1363
31.44 Cubic Feet 8 transfile boxes
Scope and Contents
This collection is comprised of select Laurance S. Rockefeller and Mary French Rockefeller cashbooks, contributions, ledgers, household account books, business account books, receipts and disbursements, expenditures, trial balances, and securities.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged materials are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Original order, as received.
- Mary French Rockefeller (MFR) Cashbook, 1948-1953 (Box T12)
- MFR Cashbook, 1954-1957 (Box T12)
- MFR Cashbook, 1958-1961 (Box T12)
- MFR Cashbook, 1961-1964 (Box T12)
- MFR Cashbook, 1965-1966 (Box T12)
- MFR General Ledger No. 1, 1967-1969 (Box T12)
- Ledger, 1969 (Box T12)
- LSR Cashbook, 1961 (Box T1)
- LSR Cashbook, 1950-1953 (Box T1)
- LSR No. 2 Account - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1947-1950 (Box T1)
- LSR Disbursements, Chase National Bank, Household and Personal Accounts, 1934-1937 (Box T1)
- LSR Disbursements, Household Account, 1938-1941 (Box T1)
- LSR Business, 1937-1946 (Box T1)
- LSR Business Account, 1947-1953 (Box T1)
- LSR Household Account, Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1947-1949 (Box T1)
- LSR Household Account, 1954-1957 (Box T1)
- LSR Cashbook Account No. 2 - Chase National Bank, 1934-1939 (Box T14)
- LSR Cashbook, 1952-1953 (Box T14)
- LSR Cashbook, 1954-1955 (Box T14)
- LSR Business Account, 1954-1958 (Box T14)
- LSR Contributions, 1930-1960 (Box T14)
- LSR Cashbook, 1957-1958 (Box T14)
- Laurance Rockefeller, Marion R. Weber Account No. 2, 1960s (Box T14)
- LSR Cashbook, 1960-1961 (Box T14)
- LSR Weekly Cash Statements (Box T31)
- 834 Fifth Avenue Apartment Expenditures (Box T31)
- LSR Household Account, 1958-1961 (Box T19)
- LSR Household and JY Ranch - General Ledger No. 1, 1962 (Box T19)
- LSR General Ledger No. 2, 1963-1964 (Box T19)
- LSR General Ledger No. 3, 1965-1966 (Box T19)
- LSR General Ledger No. 4, 1966-1967 (Box T19)
- LSR General Ledger No. 4 (Box T19)
- LSR Journal, 1958-1960 (Box T19)
- LSR - Unlabeled, 1940-1947 (Box T2)
- LSR Household, 1944-1946 (Box T2)
- LSR Household Account, 1962 (Box T2)
- Marion F. Rockefeller Cashbook, 1959-1964 (Box T2)
- LSR Household - Receipts and Disbursements, 1934-1944 (Box T2)
- LSR Cashbook, 1947-1950 (Box T2)
- LSR Cashbook, 1950-1951 (Box T2)
- LSR Cashbook, 1955-1957 (Box T2)
- LSR Cashbook, 1959-1960 (Box T2)
- Family of LSR/Mary French Rockefeller - Securities No. 1, 1937-1969 (Box T15)
- LSR General Ledger No. 1, 1961-1962 (Box T15)
- LSR Business (Box T15)
- LSR Business (Box T15)
- LSR, 1936-1940 (Box T15)
- LSR, 1940-1941 (Box T15)
- LSR, 1945-1946 (Box T15)
- LSR Trial Balances, 1971 (Box T33)
- LSR Trial Balances, 1972 (Box T33)
- MFR - 1973-1975 - Trial Balances, Cash Receipts and Disbursements, Accounting Details (Box T33)
- MFR - 1976-1979 - Trial Balances, Cash Receipts and Disbursements, Accounting Details (Box T33)
- LSR - 1973-1975 - Trial Balances, Cash Receipts and Disbursements, Accounting Details (Box T33)
- LSR - General Ledger, 1970-1972 (Box T33)
- LSR General Ledger (Box T33)
- LSR Trial Balances, 1970 (Box T33)
- MFR Trial Balances, 1970-1972 (Box T33)
- MFR Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1971-1972 (Box T33)
- MFR Stock and Bond Inventories, 1970-1972 (Box T33)
- LSR and MFR Securities, Schedule D, 1975-1977 (Box T33)